Here's the code we were just looking at.
这是我们刚刚看到的代码
If you played with this,
如果你玩这个
you should have found that when you change the turtle's name in only one line of code,
你应该发现当你改变海龟名字的时候
the program won't work.
程序就不起作用了
When you try to run it, you just get an error message.
当您尝试运行它时 只会收到一条错误消息
But if you change the name in all of these lines,
但如果你更改了所有这些行的名称
it works just fine.
那就行了
We can better understand why that's happening if we look more
我们能更好地理解为什么会发生这种情况
closely at this line: george equals turtle.Turtle.
就在这条线上 : george 等于 turtle.Turtle
On a general level, we can think of this line as
在一个普通的层面上 我们可以认为这条线
creating a turtle and giving that turtle a name.
创造一只乌龟给乌龟取名
This part on the right, turtle.Turtle parentheses,
这部分是右边的海龟
is the part that creates a new turtle and this part on the left,
是创造一个新的乌龟的部分
George, says what the turtle's name will be.
乔治说乌龟的名字会是什么
But what do we mean when we say this code is creating a turtle?
但是当我们说这个代码是在创造乌龟的时候 我们的意思是什么 ?
Well, Python has a bunch of information about how a turtle works,
Python 有很多关于海龟如何运作的信息
how to get this virtual robot to move
如何让虚拟机器人移动
around in different ways and draw things on the screen.
用不同的方式在屏幕上画东西
In order to be able to use a turtle in our program,
为了能在我们的节目中使用乌龟
we first need to make a copy of some of this data in the computer's memory.
我们首先需要在计算机的内存中复制其中一些数据
So, when we run this code, turtle.Turtle,
所以当我们运行这个代码 turtle.Turtle
Python finds some free space in
Python 找到了一些可用空间
the computer's memory and it puts this turtle data into that space.
电脑的记忆就会把这个海龟数据放进那个空间里
Basically, we're getting things ready so that we can use
基本上我们准备好了
this data whenever we need to have the turtle draw something.
只要我们需要有乌龟就能画出来
So, we now have the data we need for
我们现在有了我们需要的数据
the virtual turtle robot in this specific location in the computer's memory.
在计算机内存中的这个特定位置的虚拟海龟机器人
By the way, you'll hear us refer to this as
顺便说下你会听到我们说
a turtle data object or simply a turtle object.
乌龟数据对象或简单海龟对象
If we want to be able to use this turtle object,
如果我们想用这个乌龟物体
we can't just put the data in memory,
我们不能把数据放在记忆里
we also need to have some way of talking about that turtle,
我们也要有办法说那只乌龟
giving it instructions and so on.
给它指示等等
We need some way of referring to that turtle.
我们需要某种方式提到那只乌龟
That's why we give it a name, like George.
这就是为什么我们给它一个名字像乔治
Once the turtle data object has been placed in memory and given a name,
一旦海龟数据对象被放入记忆中并给出一个名字
we can use that name whenever we want to do something with the turtle.
只要我们想和乌龟做什么就可以用这个名字
For example, if we want the turtle named George to go forward or turn,
例如 如果我们想让叫乔治的乌龟前进或转弯
we can use lines like george.forward100 and george.right90.
我们可以使用 george.forward100 和 george.right90之类的线路
If we first say that we are referring to this data object as George but then
如果我们先说 我们指的是 George  然后是 George
later try to refer to it with a different name like Amy, it's not going to work.
然后试着用像 Amy 这样的不同的名字来称呼它 它是不会起作用的
Our code hasn't connected Amy with any particular data in memory.
我们的代码没有将 Amy 与内存中的任何特定数据连接起来
We can use pretty much whatever name we want,
我们可以用我们想要的名字
but we have to be consistent or Python won't know what data we're referring to.
但我们必须一致或 Python 不知道我们指的是什么数据
Now, this concept isn't just something that applies to naming turtles.
现在 这个概念不只是适用于命名海龟的东西
The general idea here is that we put some data into
一般的想法是我们把一些数据放进去
the computer's memory and then we connect
电脑的记忆然后我们就会
that data to a name that we can use in our code.
我们的代码中可以使用的数据
When we have a connection between a name and the code and some data in memory,
当我们有一个名字和代码之间的连接以及内存中的一些数据时
there's a specific term we use for this,
我们有一个特定的术语
it's called a variable.
它叫做变量
The reason we call it a variable is because this connection is able to vary,
我们之所以称它为变量 是因为这个连接能够改变
that is, we can change what data of variable refers to.
就是我们可以改变变量的数据是指什么
We can say this variable refers to some data in one place in memory,
我们可以说这个变量是指内存中一个地方的一些数据
but then later in our program we could change it so the variable
但后来在我们的计划中我们可以改变它
refers to some other data in a different location in memory.
指的是内存中不同位置的其他一些数据
A variable is kind of a box with a label on it.
一个变量是一个带有标签的盒子
We can use the label to refer to whatever is in that box,
我们可以用标签来指那个盒子里的任何东西
but we could later take the label off and stick it onto a different box instead.
但我们可以把标签取下来把它贴在另一个盒子上
To tell the computer that a particular data object should have a particular name tag,
要告诉计算机 特定数据对象应该具有特定名称标记
we use lines like george equals turtle.Turtle.
我们用像地质公园一样的线
Notice how this line splits into two parts around the equal sign.
请注意 此线条如何在等号周围分割为两个部分
On the right is the code turtle.Turtle,
右边是代号龟龟
which creates a new turtle.
造就了一只新的乌龟
On the left is George which is the name that we are giving to the variable.
左边是 George  这是我们给变量的名字
In the middle is the equal sign which tells Python,
中间是告诉 Python的等号
take this thing on the right and connect it with the name on the left.
把这个东西放在右边把它和左边的名字连接起来
By the way, when we connect a name with some data in memory,
顺便说下 当我们用记忆中的一些数据连接一个名字时
we refer to this process as assignment.
我们把这个过程称为赋值
We are assigning the data from the code on the right and the name on the left.
我们正在从右边的代码和左侧的名称中分配数据
The equal sign is called an assignment operator and we can refer to a line of code,
等号称为赋值运算符 我们可以引用一行代码
like george equals turtle.Turtle,
就像地质公园一样龟龟
as an assignment statement.
作为赋值语句
Notice that the stuff on the right of an assignment statement always happens first.
请注意 赋值语句右边的内容总是首先发生的
First, we create a new turtle and then we assign that turtle to the name George.
首先 我们创造一个新的乌龟 然后把乌龟分配给乔治